威尔 · 森坦斯: 让我们来谈谈这个交织在和中的执行线程
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's just talk about
this thread of execution that wove in and
编织。
wove out.
我们知道当我们运行完乘以2,
We knew that when we finished
running multiply by two,
称之为用 parens 调用它,
calling it invoking it with parens,
我们知道我们的死刑威胁会传到 global 那里。
we knew that our threat of execution
was gonna come back out to global.
我们可以直观地看到它是在全局 JavaScript 代码中运行的
We kind of visually saw that it's being
run within the code of global JavaScript
需要做更多的工作，这是一个更准确和精确的轨道,
needs to do more work on that is a track
that more accurately and precisely,
它有一个叫做调用堆栈的功能。
it has something called
the call stack to do, so.
追踪当前正在运行的函数
JavaScript keeps track of what
function is currently running by using
这是我们理解平台的最后一部分
this final part of our platform
of understanding our platform
调用栈是 JavaScript 引擎的一部分。
of the JavaScript engine
called the call stack.
这是一种在我们的电脑上储存信息的传统方式,
Here it is, it is a traditional way of
storing information on our computer,
我们有很多种方法，数组，对象,
we have a number of ways,
arrays, we have objects,
我们还有所谓的堆栈。
we also have what's called stacks.
我们不会深入研究他们的前提，但是
We're not gonna go deeply
into their premise, but
堆栈的一个关键问题是，当你在堆栈中添加一些东西时,
a key thing with a stack is
when you add something to it,
当你运行一个函数时，我们要把它添加到调用堆栈中。
when you run a function we're
going to add it to our call stack.
所以当我们开始运行乘以2的时候,
So when we started running
multiply by two up here,
我们把它加到调用堆栈中，乘以2再加上3的输入。
we add it to our call stack,
multiply by two with the input of three.
现在 JavaScript 已经确定了当前正在运行的代码在哪里
Now JavaScript has certainty of
what is currently running where is
我们的行刑线索吗？
our thread of execution right now?
因为一个关键的单一规则和
Well, it's busy inside a multiple by two,
cuz the one key single rule and
我们只和一个非常非常重要的东西打交道,
stack is we're only engaged with a very,
very top thing on it,
这是我们唯一能接触到的东西。
that's the only thing
we're interacting with.
所以不管调用堆栈的顶部是什么，那就是我们现在所处的位置。
So whatever's at the top of the call
stack, that's where we are right now.
只要我们运行完这个函数，并且
As soon as we finish
running that function, and
顺便说一句，亚当，事实上，杰夫？
by the way, Adam, actually, [SOUND] Jeff?
Jeff 告诉我们我们已经完成了一个函数的执行,
Jeff, what, Jeff tells us,
we have finished executing a function,
什么关键字说，结束这个功能，继续前进。
what keywords says,
end this function, move on.
讲者二: 报税表。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Return.
Will Sentance: 完全返回，只要我们点击返回这个函数
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Return exactly,
as soon as we hit return this function
执行上下文从调用堆栈中弹出，那么最重要的是什么？
execution context popped off
the call stack, so what's top?
这是不令人印象深刻的，那么现在调用堆栈的顶部是什么？
That was underwhelming, so
what is top of the call stack now?
有什么问题吗？
Well is there anything?
是的，总是在呼叫堆栈底部的人是我们的全球
Yeah, always on the bottom of
the call stack folk is our global
执行上下文。
execution context.
考虑一下全局标签函数中的所有代码，以及
Think of all of our code inside
a function with the label global, and
一旦我们打开 JavaScript 开始运行代码,
as soon as we turn on JavaScript,
start running the code,
运行那个全局函数，运行整个代码。
run that global function
run the overall code.
所以一旦你开始运行 JavaScript,
So that's always as soon as
you start running JavaScript,
在底部加上 global。
global is added on the bottom.
所以当我们开始运行乘以2的时候，我们把它加到最上面,
And that's always there, so when we start
running multiply by two we add it on top,
当我们运行完它，我们移除它，然后我们回到哪里？
when we finish running it, we remove it,
and where do we go back to?
别慌电话里还有什么情况 Kayla？
Well don't panic,
what's left on the call stat, Kayla?
讲者三: 全球 威尔 · 森坦斯: 全球化，就是这样,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Global.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Global, and there it is,
太好了，谢谢你，凯拉，就是这样，当我们开始运行乘以2
excellent, thank you Kayla, there it is,
when we start running multiply by two
再加上10的输入，我们把它加到调用松弛上，就是这样。
again with the input of 10, we add
it onto the call slack, there it is.
当我们运行完之后，我们把它取下来，JavaScript 不会慌乱，然后,
When we finish running it, we take it off,
and JavaScript doesn't panic and go,
我该去哪儿？
where do I go?
回到全局，如果我在 multimyby2中运行另一个函数,
It goes back to global, if I were to run
another function inside of multiplyBy2,
然后在上面加一个，再在里面加一个，然后加到上面。
that would be added on top, another inside
of that, that would be added on top.
运行完那个程序，我要回局里吗？
Finish running that one,
do I go back to global?
我回到我开始运行这个功能的地方，换句话说，把它关掉
I go back to wherever I started running
that function, in other words, take it off
这是堆栈的关键前提。
the stack and about where I was before and
that's the key premise of a stack.
好的，但是我们会看到更多的酷的一面
Okay, but we're gonna see the cool side
quite a bit more over the session where
有个通话功能。
there's a call feature.
这就是人们，这就是 JavaScript 的三个核心组件,
That is it people, that is the three
core components of JavaScript,
当我们一行一行地检查代码时，我们有存储数据的记忆。
we have our memory to store data as
we go through the code line by line.
令人惊讶的是，我们可以存储代码功能，然后我们可以运行
And amazingly, to store code
functionality, and we can then run and
触发运行代码时，我们想要，这不是一件小事,
trigger to run code whenever we want,
that's not a small thing,
真是不可思议。
that's quite remarkable.
在排序数据中，我们看到了运行的代码，仔细想想，你真的可以
And in a sort data, we saw code to run,
think about it, you're literally able to
随时在你的代码中启动一个你自己选择的小程序。
start a little mini program of your
choice at any moment in your code.
然后，我们有一个执行线程，一行一行地检查代码,
And, then we have the thread of execution
to go through the code line by line,
它大部分时间都在存储数据，但它同时也把一些存储的数据
a lot of the time it's storing data,
but it's also taking some of the stored
然后说开始运行它。
functionality code and
saying start running it.
我们创建了一个小程序一个小子程序,
We create a little mini program,
a little sub-program,
我们进入的执行环境
a execution context into which we go and
当我们在那个函数里的时候，把我们存储的所有数据划分开来。
compartmentalize any data we're storing
while we're inside that function.
当我们退出该函数时，除了返回的内容外，所有内容都被删除了,
When we exit that function, all is
deleted, besides whatever we return out,
实际上我们可以看到所有的都被删除了,
let's actually show that all is deleted,
the size,
无论我们返回什么，然后运行另一个函数也是这样。
whatever we return out, and
then run another function do the same.
我们跟踪我们正在运行的函数
We keep track of the functions
we're running and
我们的执行线程正在使用我们的调用栈。
where our thread of execution
is using our call stack.